[
  {
     "question":
         {
          "prompt": "The dog went for him.",
          "optionA": "a) The dog barked at him.",
          "optionB": "b) The dog attacked him.",
          "optionC": "c) The dog followed him.",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
      "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She hadn't bargained for this.",
          "optionA": "a) She hadn't expected this.",
          "optionB": "b) She hadn't bought this.",
          "optionC": "c) She hadn't profited from this.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "It suddenly dawned on her.",
          "optionA": "a) She suddenly turned the lights on.",
          "optionB": "b) She suddenly realised.",
          "optionC": "c) She was suddenly seen.",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
      "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I feel for you.",
          "optionA": "a) I am fond of you.",
          "optionB": "b) I pity you.",
          "optionC": "c) I sympathise for you.",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She got over her illness.",
          "optionA": "a) She learned from her ilness.",
          "optionB": "b) She died from her ilness.",
          "optionC": "c) She recovered from her illness.",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "The police looked into it.",
          "optionA": "a) The police didn't care about it.",
          "optionB": "b) The police ivestigated it.",
          "optionC": "c) The police looked inside it.",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "They talked it over.",
          "optionA": "a) They discussed it.",
          "optionB": "b) They talked a lot.",
          "optionC": "c) They gossiped.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She did up her laces.",
          "optionA": "a) She tied her laces.",
          "optionB": "b) She painted her laces.",
          "optionC": "c) She sewed her laces.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He called on her.",
          "optionA": "a) He telephoned her.",
          "optionB": "b) He visited her.",
          "optionC": "c) He blamed her.",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She made for the living room.",
          "optionA": "a) She went towards the living room.",
          "optionB": "b) She paid to build the living room.",
          "optionC": "c) She decorated the living room.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He launched into a long speech.",
          "optionA": "a) He improvised a long speech.",
          "optionB": "b) He got lost in his long speech.",
          "optionC": "c) He began a long speech.",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He takes after his mother.",
          "optionA": "a) He has the same profession as his mother.",
          "optionB": "b) He looks like his mother.",
          "optionC": "c) He is like his mother.",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "She came up with the solution.",
          "optionA": "a) She refused the solution.",
          "optionB": "b) She thought of the solution.",
          "optionC": "c) She couldn't understand the solution.",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He pointed out the mall would be closed.",
          "optionA": "a) He informed the mall would be closed.",
          "optionB": "a) He forgot the mall would be closed.",
          "optionC": "a) He remembered the mall would be closed.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "It was easy to find out the answer.",
          "optionA": "a) It was easy to forget the answer.",
          "optionB": "b) It was easy to share the answer.",
          "optionC": "c) It was easy to discover the answer.",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "Who's going to take on the new client?",
          "optionA": "a) Who's going to be responsible for the new client?",
          "optionB": "b) Who's going to bring the new client?",
          "optionC": "Who's going to talk to the new client?",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "When are we setting up the next meeting?",
          "optionA": "a) When are we recording the next meeting?",
          "optionB": "b) When are we arranging the next meeting?",
          "optionC": "c) When are we beginning the next meeting?",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "He will not back down on his decision.",
          "optionA": "a) He will not change his mind about his decision",
          "optionB": "b) He will not think about his decision.",
          "optionC": "c) He won't ellaborate his decision.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "Book in at the reception.",
          "optionA": "a) Take your book at the reception",
          "optionB": "b) Pay for the book at the reception",
          "optionC": "c) Register at the reception",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
  },
  {
     "question":
        {
          "prompt": "I can't piece together the truth about it.",
          "optionA": "a) I can't discover the truth about it.",
          "optionB": "b) I can't hide the truth about it.",
          "optionC": "c) I can't deny the truth about it.",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   }
]